<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cisco on FullStackGeek</title>
    <link>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/tags/cisco/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cisco on FullStackGeek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 16:55:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.fullstackgeek.net/tags/cisco/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>First impressions on CWOM – a less green Turbonomic</title>
      <link>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2017/10/26/first-impressions-on-cwom-a-less-green-turbonomic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 16:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2017/10/26/first-impressions-on-cwom-a-less-green-turbonomic/</guid>
      <description>Early this year, there were talks of Cisco acquiring Turbonomic. A few months back this became a partnership to release Cisco Workload Optimization Manager (CWOM). This is one of the newest products included in the Cisco ONE Enterprise Cloud Suite.
Cisco Workload Optimization Manager is now in its 1.1.3 release. Starting with this release, you can target UCS Director as an orchestration target. I would love to leverage this, I now need to get UCS Director back into the environment).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Potential upgrade issues going to Cisco UCS Manager 3.2(1d)</title>
      <link>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2017/08/27/potential-upgrade-issues-upgrades-ucsm-321d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 20:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2017/08/27/potential-upgrade-issues-upgrades-ucsm-321d/</guid>
      <description>We recently upgraded a few of our UCS domains from 3.1(1h) and 3.1(2b) up to 3.2(1d) and we had issues with a few IO modules hanging for up to 2 hours with trying to activate the firmware.
The backup version was updated with no issues, but then the activation stalled through anywhere from 16 to 30 tries before failing.
We decided to leave most of the faulted IOMs alone to see what they would do, but after 2 hours we decided to attempt a reset of one IO module, and that just made it angry&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
