<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blogtober on FullStackGeek</title>
    <link>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/tags/blogtober/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blogtober on FullStackGeek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 23:50:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.fullstackgeek.net/tags/blogtober/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exagrid Installation and Initialization</title>
      <link>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2017/10/30/exagrid-installation-and-initialization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 23:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2017/10/30/exagrid-installation-and-initialization/</guid>
      <description>We are testing out two new ExaGrid 40000E appliances. These will be new initial target repositories for backups from Veeam Backup &amp;amp; Recovery. This is a prime opportunity to get out another article about the install and initialization of the ExaGrid hardware. I intend to follow with a post about the benefits of the Veeam integration.
ExaGrid is an exceptional idea for their layout with the distinct partitions of a &amp;ldquo;landing zone&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;retention zone&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First impressions on CWOM – a less green Turbonomic</title>
      <link>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2017/10/26/first-impressions-on-cwom-a-less-green-turbonomic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 16:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2017/10/26/first-impressions-on-cwom-a-less-green-turbonomic/</guid>
      <description>Early this year, there were talks of Cisco acquiring Turbonomic. A few months back this became a partnership to release Cisco Workload Optimization Manager (CWOM). This is one of the newest products included in the Cisco ONE Enterprise Cloud Suite.
Cisco Workload Optimization Manager is now in its 1.1.3 release. Starting with this release, you can target UCS Director as an orchestration target. I would love to leverage this, I now need to get UCS Director back into the environment).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Own The Imposter Syndrome</title>
      <link>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2017/10/25/own-the-imposter-syndrome/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 18:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2017/10/25/own-the-imposter-syndrome/</guid>
      <description>Howdy, this is Joe Houghes. I&amp;rsquo;d like to introduce myself some in my first real post before I try and speak about technical content. This has been a big year of change for me with regards to my career, personal life, and social presence. As such, I want to share some reflection. This relates to my own experience as someone new to sharing knowledge with others.
I&amp;rsquo;m a run of the mill 35-year-old out of shape IT geek who is a native of Austin, Texas.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
