<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Work on FullStackGeek</title>
    <link>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/categories/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Work on FullStackGeek</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 14:13:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.fullstackgeek.net/categories/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Migrating to Cloud and Running Hybrid: Part 5 - Azure &amp; AVS</title>
      <link>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2024/10/21/migrating-to-cloud-and-running-hybrid-part5-azure-avs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 14:13:21 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2024/10/21/migrating-to-cloud-and-running-hybrid-part5-azure-avs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For our final technical post in the series, we will look at Microsoft Azure as the public cloud to target for migrating workloads.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Similar to our previous post, we are going to look at some of the options that customers have available to them for migrating on-prem workloads to Azure – we&amp;rsquo;ll mention AVS later in the post, but that one is almost cheating.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since our second post in the series got our data handled for being separated from the OS and replicated to the cloud, let&amp;rsquo;s see what we can use to move the workloads themselves  this time around.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating to Cloud and Running Hybrid: Part 4 - AWS</title>
      <link>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2024/10/17/migrating-to-cloud-and-running-hybrid-part4-aws/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 14:13:21 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2024/10/17/migrating-to-cloud-and-running-hybrid-part4-aws/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For our second technical post in the series, we will look at Amazon Web Services (AWS) as the public cloud to target for migrating workloads.&#xA;We are going to look at some of the options that customers have available to them for migrating on-prem workloads to AWS.  We already have our data handled through the methods we discussed in the last blog post, so now we are talking about getting the workloads themselves up to the cloud.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating to Cloud and Running Hybrid: Part 3 - Guest OS &amp; Replication</title>
      <link>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2024/10/12/migrating-to-cloud-and-running-hybrid-part3-guestos-replication/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2024 14:13:21 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2024/10/12/migrating-to-cloud-and-running-hybrid-part3-guestos-replication/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If the environment that is being moved to a new platform is not VMware-based, or if vVols are not an option for some reason, then we moved to the next layer down and look at the performing data migrations from within an operating system.  This is going to be performed by enabling &amp;amp; configuring iSCSI within Windows or Linux, creating a host object in the FlashArray with the IQN initiator for the iSCSI initiator, and then mapping a volume to this new host object on the FlashArray.  Once the device is visible within the operating system, the raw device should be formatted with the appropriate file system option for the intended usage, and this newly formatted device can then be used for data migration. At this point, we need to discuss a few options and considerations which will be different for Windows versus Linux operating systems, and warn you that you should always have proper planning and backups in place prior to data conversions or migrations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating to Cloud and Running Hybrid: Part 2 - vVols</title>
      <link>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2024/10/11/migrating-to-cloud-and-running-hybrid-part2-vVols/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 14:13:21 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2024/10/11/migrating-to-cloud-and-running-hybrid-part2-vVols/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Continuing directly from our last blog post, let&amp;rsquo;s jump in if we need to get to a lower level than VM disks within a hypervisor.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For our second (and longer) post in the series, we will look at some of the core functionality of Pure Storage which will be used to help any customer migrate workloads, and I am talking about volume management and replication.  For many customers that are considering moving VMware workloads to any new platform, one of the easiest ways to be successful with a &amp;ldquo;replatform&amp;rdquo; for any workloads is to separate the data that needs to move platforms from the core operating system.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating to Cloud and Running Hybrid: Part 1 - Ugh</title>
      <link>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2024/10/08/migrating-to-cloud-and-running-hybrid-part1-ugh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 14:13:21 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2024/10/08/migrating-to-cloud-and-running-hybrid-part1-ugh/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These days, businesses are realizing that sticking to just one cloud or one type of environment doesn’t cut it anymore. The reality is, most organizations need the flexibility to run workloads wherever it makes the most sense—whether that’s in their own on-premises setup, in the cloud, or a mix of both.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A hybrid approach can be a game-changer, letting companies keep critical data or legacy systems on-prem while still taking advantage of the scalability and innovation that public cloud platforms offer. But it doesn’t stop there. As things change—whether it’s costs, technical needs, or capacity—workloads often need to shift between clouds.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating Your Pure Storage Infrastructure: Part 4 - Protection Group Snapshots - SDK1 and SDK2</title>
      <link>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2024/07/19/automating-your-pure-storage-infrastructure-part4-protection-group-snapshots-sdk1-and-sdk2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 14:13:21 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2024/07/19/automating-your-pure-storage-infrastructure-part4-protection-group-snapshots-sdk1-and-sdk2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For this next example, we will look at a request which came into from a customer looking to see if there is a way to list the volumes in a protection group snapshot.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll look at how we can produce this output with 2 different methods:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Continue with our use of PureStoragePowerShellSDK (the original v1 SDK) and the &amp;lsquo;New-PfaCLICommand&amp;rsquo; cmdlet&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Look at the use of PureStoragePowerShellSDK2 to gather these details&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While the command that we will use to gather these results from our FlashArray are different, method 1 is the same as our previous blog posts on the process of wrapping CLI commands into PowerShell to work with the results with the addition of using &lt;code&gt;Out-GridView&lt;/code&gt; for the selection of a specific Protection Group (pgroup) snapshot.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating Your Pure Storage Infrastructure: Part 3 - Host Port Mapping with SDK1</title>
      <link>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2024/07/15/automating-your-pure-storage-infrastructure-part3-host-port-mapping-with-sdk1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 14:13:21 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2024/07/15/automating-your-pure-storage-infrastructure-part3-host-port-mapping-with-sdk1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In our third post in our series, we&amp;rsquo;re going to take the code that we produced previously to gather additional information for the request of a detailed host mapping that can give a comparison of pre and post upgrade to verify that all of the paths match.  In the code from our previous post, we were able to gather the information he needed about the connected initiators from the array perspective. Now, we need to gather the information about our hosts and their registered initiators, then tie that information together.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating Your Pure Storage Infrastructure: Part 2 - Active Port Connections with SDK1</title>
      <link>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2024/07/11/automating-your-pure-storage-infrastructure-part2-active-port-connections-with-sdk1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 14:13:21 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2024/07/11/automating-your-pure-storage-infrastructure-part2-active-port-connections-with-sdk1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Now for step 2 in our blog series, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at the CLI output which will give us the details that we are looking for, so we can work towards our &amp;ldquo;grouped by host&amp;rdquo; requirement.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The CLI command which will give us the results we are looking for is &lt;code&gt;pureport list&lt;/code&gt; with the &amp;ldquo;initiator&amp;rdquo; parameter, and a basic run of this CLI command in an SSH session gives us this output:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating Your Pure Storage Infrastructure: Part 1 - Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2024/07/09/automating-your-pure-storage-infrastructure-part1-getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:13:21 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.fullstackgeek.net/2024/07/09/automating-your-pure-storage-infrastructure-part1-getting-started/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After a decently long hiatus from writing anything in a series-fashion, I&amp;rsquo;m back to share a blog series based around automating your Pure Storage environment.  We&amp;rsquo;re going to begin this series with a few posts about advancing both your understanding of your Pure Storage environment and understanding the options available to you for automating and monitoring the infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This series will begin with some requests that came from Pure Storage customers, and other Pure employees that asked for some help in delivering the solution, or just some help with understanding how to accomplish the goal.  These are normally the most enjoyable tasks to automate, as it gives a chance to understand what sorts of tasks a customer is trying to accomplish and what needs they have, and to help educate others along the way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
